nzqa.govt.nz 2010-06-24

# Conditions of use [ NZQA ]

|  |  | About NZQA  
---|---  
  
These conditions of use apply to your browsing and use of this website. Please read them before continuing to browse this website. Use of this website is deemed to be acceptance of these conditions of use. Three areas are covered: 

  * Disclaimer
  * Copyright
  * Privacy 

##  Privacy 

You may browse and access some information contained within this website without providing any personal information. However, where you voluntarily provide personal information or where you are requested to provide personal information to access certain areas of the site or perform certain functions, such information will be held by NZQA. If you do not provide the information requested, you will not be able to access those parts of the website. 

Where you are requested to provide personal information, the relevant part of the website will inform you of the reason that information is sought. We will only use that information in a manner that is lawful. 

NZQA will take all practicable steps to keep any personal information you provide secure. Unless required or permitted by law, NZQA will not make your personal information available to third parties in a way that identifies you. However, NZQA shall not be liable for any loss of privacy, disclosure of information, harm, damage or loss that may result from your transmission or sending of information to NZQA in connection with this website. 

The Privacy Act 1993 gives you the right to see and correct information that NZQA holds about you. If you want to access the information held about you by NZQA, or if you would like to correct any such information held, or if you have any privacy concerns, please contact the NZQA Privacy Officer.

###  Note regarding cookies 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Unless required or permitted by law, personal information collected through the use of cookies is used by NZQA to monitor usage of its website and will not be made available to third parties in a manner which enables you to be identified. If your browser blocks cookies, NZQA's webs systems will continue to work. 

Page updated: Tue Apr 13 00:00:00 NZST 2010
